♪They say time will reveal a person's heart♪
♪ يقولون الوقت سيكشف قلب الإنسان
♪In all lives, may the sea calm the tides♪
في كل حيوات البحر يهدئ المد والجزر
♪Blue silk drifting to one's hometown, carrying greed, hatred, and ignorance♪
حرير أزرق ينجرف إلى مسقط رأس المرء حاملاً الجشع والكراهية والجهل ♪
♪Going to the corners of the heavens to seek a long-awaited reunion♪
الذهاب إلى أركان السماء بحثًا عن لم الشمل الذي طال انتظاره ♪
♪To live or die together, that is but an act♪
أن نعيش معًا أو نموت معًا ، فهذا ليس سوى فعل
♪Letting down our memories♪
تخلي ذكرياتنا ♪
♪Why should we rip out our heart for a heartless person?♪
♪ لماذا يجب أن نقطع قلوبنا من أجل إنسان بلا قلب؟
♪Treating each other with courtesy is but a scene in my dream♪
معاملة بعضنا البعض بلطف ليس سوى مشهد في حلمي
♪We'll wake up eventually♪
♪ سنستيقظ في النهاية ♪
♪As the autumn wind blows, the maple leaves fall, pulling myself away♪
♪ مع هبوب رياح الخريف ، تتساقط أوراق القيقب ، وتسحب نفسي بعيدًا ♪
=Don't Forget My Love= =Episode 13=
= لا تنسى حبي = = الحلقة 13 =
Father,
أب،
please rescind the order.
يرجى إلغاء الأمر.
I will marry Yun Qianyu
سوف أتزوج يون Qianyu
no matter what.
بغض النظر.
Insolence!
وقاحة!
It was Prime Minister Yun who wanted to call the marriage off.
كان رئيس الوزراء يون هو من أراد إلغاء الزواج.
He has humiliated me!
لقد أهانني!
Father,
أب،
rumours are spreading among the people
الشائعات تنتشر بين الناس
that
الذي - التي
the fall of the Prime Minister's family
سقوط عائلة رئيس الوزراء
is the deed of the imperial family.
هو صك العائلة الإمبراطورية.
I intend
أنوي
to marry her
لتتزوجها
to silence those rumours.
لإسكات تلك الشائعات.
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
you gave me a scare!
لقد أصبت بالفزع!
I can't believe
لا أستطيع أن أصدق
you dared to oppose His Majesty in court.
لقد تجرأت على معارضة جلالة الملك في المحكمة.
I once thought
اعتقدت ذات مرة
that no matter
هذا لا يهم
who I chose to marry,
الذي اخترت الزواج منه ،
it would only be a mutual agreement
سيكون فقط اتفاق متبادل
to serve both of our needs.
لخدمة كل من احتياجاتنا.
But now,
لكن الآن،
I actually find myself partial
في الواقع أجد نفسي متحيزًا
to marrying her.
للزواج منها.
Daughter of Yun Haotian, Yun Qianyu, receive the imperial edict.
تلقت Yun Qianyu ، ابنة Yun Haotian ، المرسوم الإمبراطوري.
An imperial decree from His Majesty.
مرسوم إمبراطوري من جلالة الملك.
His Majesty is deeply saddened by the murder of Prime Minister Yun's family.
جلالة الملك يشعر بحزن عميق لمقتل أسرة رئيس الوزراء يون.
The Yulin Army has been tasked to investigate the matter
تم تكليف جيش يولين بالتحقيق في الأمر
and apprehend the culprit
والقبض على الجاني
to console the prime minister's soul in heaven.
لتعزية روح رئيس الوزراء في الجنة.
Yun Haotian made great contributions and shall be given
قدم يون هاوتيان مساهمات كبيرة وستعطى
the posthumous title of Grace Defender Duke.
لقب غريس ديفندر ديوك بعد وفاته.
His daughter, Yun Qianyu,
ابنته ، يون Qianyu ،
is good-natured and well-educated.
حسن النية ومتعلم جيدًا.
She will hereby be named Crown Princess.
ستسمى بموجب هذا ولي العهد.
As she is currently in mourning, the date of her moving
كما هي حاليا في حداد موعد انتقالها
into the Crown Prince's palace may be postponed.
في قصر ولي العهد قد يؤجل.
That is all.
هذا كل شيء.
There is no need
لا حاجة لذلك
to postpone the date.
لتأجيل الموعد.
(Qingyun Palace)
(قصر تشينغيون)
In Dayu, it is customary to comb the hair of the bride before she is wed.
في Dayu ، من المعتاد تمشيط شعر العروس قبل الزواج.
His Highness sent me
أرسلني سموه
to comb Your Highness's hair.
لتمشيط شعر سموك.
May the crown prince and crown princess be together for life.
أتمنى أن يكون ولي العهد وولي العهد معًا مدى الحياة.
May you be blessed
نرجو أن تبارك
with prosperity and abundance.
مع الرخاء والوفرة.
May your marriage
أتمنى أن يكون زواجك
be blessed with harmony.
تبارك بالوئام.
May your hearts
نرجو قلوبكم
be forever tied as one.
كن مقيدًا إلى الأبد كواحد.
It's His Highness's wedding day.
إنه يوم زفاف سموه.
Be quick and efficient.
كن سريعًا وفعالًا.
Mistakes
اخطاء
will not be tolerated.
لن يتم التسامح معها.
Wait.
انتظر.
His Highness has ordered
أمر صاحب السمو
all of these to be changed to jelly cakes.
يتم تغيير كل هذه إلى كعك الجيلي.
It's Her Highness's favourite.
إنه المفضل لدى صاحبة السمو.
Yes.
نعم.
Go on.
تابع.
(You look beautiful, Young Lady.)
(تبدين جميلة ، سيدة شابة).
Anyone
أي واحد
would be captivated by your beauty.
سوف يأسر جمالك.
Tao,
تاو
you are getting cheekier.
أنت تزداد صدقًا.
I am telling the truth.
انا اقول الحقيقة.
I wonder who will have the fortune of marrying our young lady.
أتساءل من سيحظى بثروة الزواج من سيدتنا الشابة.
(I am certain you will look stunning in your wedding gown.)
(أنا متأكد من أنك ستبدو مذهلة في ثوب الزفاف الخاص بك.)
Your Highness,
صاحب السمو ،
it is about time.
إنها مسألة وقت.
Allow me
اسمح لي
to dress you.
لباس لكم.
Madam,
سيدتي،
you may leave now.
يمكنك الانصراف الآن.
I would like a moment to myself.
أود لحظة لنفسي.
Yes, Your Highness.
نعم سموكم.
Chi,
تشي ،
do you think
هل تعتقد
if I hadn't tried to get out of the marriage,
إذا لم أحاول الخروج من الزواج ،
Father would...
سوف الأب ...
Young Lady,
إمرأة شابة،
actually, Prime Minister Yun...
في الواقع ، رئيس الوزراء يون ...
Are you hiding something from me?
هل تخفي شيئًا عني؟
I...
أنا...
I found this when I was going through
لقد وجدت هذا عندما كنت أذهب
Prime Minister Yun's belongings.
متعلقات رئيس الوزراء يون.
The massacre wasn't a case of revenge.
لم تكن المذبحة حالة انتقام.
It was the doing of the imperial family.
كان من فعل العائلة الإمبراطورية.
♪My longing knows no bounds, in memories I wallow♪
شوقي لا يعرف حدودا ، في الذكريات أغمق ♪
♪Us and our wishful thinking♪
♪ لنا وتفكيرنا بالتمني ♪
♪When memories turn into poetry♪
عندما تتحول الذكريات إلى شعر ♪
♪Which poem will be yours?♪
♪ أي قصيدة ستكون لك؟ ♪
♪Year after year, an instant change♪
♪ سنة بعد سنة ، تغيير فوري
♪The few nights that contain our memories♪
الليالي القليلة التي تحتوي على ذكرياتنا ♪
♪Looking as the stars vanish, you grew distant from me♪
♪ بالنظر إلى اختفاء النجوم ، ابتعدت عني
♪Why can't I forget about you?♪
♪ لماذا لا أنساك؟
♪Words after words, tears flowing down♪
♪ كلمات تلو الكلمات ، الدموع تتدفق ♪
♪As the trees and plants wither♪
كما تذبل الأشجار والنباتات
♪Where are you during New Year's Eve?♪
♪ أين أنت في ليلة رأس السنة؟
♪Can you please look back?♪
♪ هل يمكنك الرجوع للوراء من فضلك؟
♪Just once♪
♪ مرة واحدة فقط ♪